Proudly Hosting over 100,000 Fast Websites since 2010

    ######  CPANEL HOSTING
    
    * 
    
    ######  RESELLER HOSTING
    
    * 
    
    ######  VPS HOSTING
    
    * 
    
    ######  DEDICATED SERVER
    
    * 
    * 
    
    ######  APPLICATION HOSTING
    
    * 
    
    ###### We are always here to provide you the best support 24x7

* Sign In

##### Sign In

×

Sign In

#### Overview

Host4Geeks LLC is a web hosting and cloud services provider registered in the state of Wyoming, US and headquartered in Walnut, CA with its datacenters in the US, UK, and India. We provide web hosting solutions including shared, reseller, dedicated servers and virtual private servers to our customers (“Services”) Host4Geeks LLC respects the privacy of every individual who visits www.host4geeks.com (“Website”) and/or purchases its Services. This Privacy Policy is our commitment to transparency in communicating how Host4Geeks collects, uses, and discloses the information that is collected from you, the visitor of its website and/or customer as well as the choices you have with respect to the information.

#### Scope of Policy  

This Privacy Policy applies to how we collect, use, and disclose information from the following individuals:

**Customers** – individuals who register, on their own or on behalf of an entity, to use our services with the creation of a client account.

**Event/Marketing Participants** – individuals who provide their information to when they register for webinars, subscribe to marketing material, participate in surveys or contests, or attend other Host4Geeks events.

**Website Visitors** – individuals who visit Host4Geek’s Website and opt to provide contact information including an email address to receive communications from Host4Geeks. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, a Website Visitor does not include an individual who visits a website hosted by Host4Geeks but owned and operated by a Host4Geeks customer.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to a Customer’s website. Our Customers are responsible for the information they or their end-users store in our hosting environment as well as compliance with applicable laws and regulations.

#### COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES

Host4Geeks uses cookies, beacons, tags, and other tracking technologies to gather demographic information about you, identify your visits to our Website, other interactions with our Website, and personalize your search experience on our Website. We gather information such as internet protocol (IP) addresses, internet service provider (ISP), operating system, browser type, date/time stamp, and store it in log files. To collect this information, a cookie, a standard feature of a website that allows us to store a small amount of data on your computer to allow our web servers to recognize you, may be set on your computer or device when you visit our Website. We may track your use across different websites and services. In some countries, including those in the European Economic Area (“EEA”), the information in this paragraph may be considered personal information under applicable data protection laws.

You can control how websites use cookies by changing your cookie settings (www.aboutcookies.org), but your modification may limit your use and functionality of some of the features on our Website. We may also use cookies and other tracking technologies to provide you advertising based on your browsing activities. You may opt-out of targeted advertisements by visiting http://optout.networkadvertising.org, or if located in the EEA, you may opt-out by visiting http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/.

#### HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

Host4Geeks uses the information it collects about you in the following ways:

* To respond to any requests from you regarding sales and support.
* To contact you regarding any agreements or accepted terms that you may have with Host4Geeks for the Services.
* To provide you with marketing emails, special offers, advertising campaigns, or newsletters.
* To provide you with information logs associated with the use of Host4Geeks’s Services.
* To contact you regarding functionality changes to our Services or Website.
* To develop new features and functionality to our Services and Website.
* To collect payment and bill for our Services.
* To help personalize searches.
* To diagnose problems.
* To find and prevent fraud.
* To register your domain.
* To carry out other purposes as disclosed to you through the Website, or found in terms or an agreement between you and Host4Geeks.
* Process for other purposes for which we obtain your consent.

#### HOW WE SHARE INFORMATION

Host4Geeks shares the information it collects about you in the following ways:

* **Third-Party Providers** – Host4Geeks may share your information with third-party providers that provide services on our behalf or resellers who provide Host4Geeks Services. These companies may assist with marketing support, processing credit card payments, content delivery, email, providing sales leads, and customer support. Third-party providers may only process personal information pursuant to Host4Geeks’s instructions and in compliance with the Privacy Policy.
* **Advertising** – Based on the cookies and other tracking devices, we may work with advertising companies to display ads that may be of interest to you.
* **Business Transactions** – To provide information to a third party in the event of any disposition of all or any portion of our business (e.g. reorganization, sale, assignment, bankruptcy).
* **Aggregated or De-identified Data** – We may disclose or use aggregated or de-identified information with third-party providers for research purposes relating to our Services.
* **As Required by Law or Similar Investigations** – To comply with legal obligations (e.g. subpoena) or investigate potential legal violations. Host4Geeks may be required to share personal data in response to lawful requests from public authorities including to meet national security and/or law enforcement requirements.
* **Safety** – We may disclose your information to protect and defend the safety of Host4Geeks in connection with investigating and preventing fraud or security issues.
* **Consent** – Host4Geeks may share your information with your consent.

#### LEGAL BASIS FOR PROCESSING PERSONAL INFORMATION

Individuals located in the EEA may have additional statutory rights available to them with respect to their personal information, including the right to access your personal information, have it erased, have it corrected, or object to or restrict processing. If you would like to make such a request, please email us and we will respond within thirty (30) days. Host4Geeks will need to verify that the individual is inquiring about his/her own information before we can assist with the request.

#### DATA SUBJECT RIGHTS

For individuals in the EEA, Host4Geeks’s legal basis for collecting and using your personal information will depend on the personal information collected and the specific context in which we collect it. Host4Geeks will process personal information from you where, a) we have your consent to do so, b) where processing is necessary for Host4Geeks to perform Services pursuant to an agreement, or c) where processing is in our legitimate interests and not overridden by your data protection interests or fundamental rights and freedoms. In some cases, we may also have a legal obligation to collect personal information, or may otherwise need personal information to protect your vital interests or those of another person. At any time, you have the right to withdraw or decline consent. If you do not provide the requested information, Host4Geeks will not be able to perform Services for you. Also, you have the right to object where we rely on our legitimate interests to process your personal information.

#### Children

Our Website and/or Services are not directed at children and our services are designed for businesses. We do not knowingly collect information from or about children under 13 years of age, and the use of our services by children under 13 years of age is forbidden.

#### Changes to Privacy Policy

Host4Geeks reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, however, should we change the Privacy Policy in a material way, a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated Privacy Policy. If you disagree with the changes, you may terminate your Services.

#### CONTACT US

If you have any questions or concerns over this Privacy Policy or wish to exercise any of your statutory rights, please contact us at:

Host4Geeks, LLC  
Attn: Legal  
340S Lemon Ave.  
Walnut, CA  
USA

AWARD-WINNING SUPPORT TEAM

### Any questions? Get in touch, our friendly team of experts will be glad to assist.

14 years in business, hosting over 100,000 websites.

Hosting

Services

Company

Resources

* [\[email protected\]](https://host4geeks.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

© 2024 Host4Geeks LLC – All Rights Reserved
